hey guys so this video is going to be a
little different than usual but I just
found it too fascinating to pass up it
doesn't have much to do with
spirituality it's more about technology
theoretical physics and science fiction
so if that's not your cup of tea feel
free to skip out on this
one also this video was inspired by
Bashar who I've just recently come
across and I'm currently binge watching
a lot of his talks for those of you who
aren't aware Bashar is supposedly an
extraterrestrial entity channeled
through a man called Daryl Anka now
Daryl has been doing this for the past
40 years or so and I recently was
introduced to him through a popular
YouTube channel called Next Level Soul
where he did a podcast interview with
the host of that
show I was impressed by the quality of
his insights and explanations and so
looked up more of this Bashar character
and got to say the more I see the more
impressed I am but if you are more of a
skeptic minded left brain person who
doesn't believe in things like
channeling this again may not be for
you personally I'm open to that
possibility and given the quality of his
answers tend to believe that he is
indeed channeling some higher Force
whether that is in fact a physical alien
somewhere else in the Galaxy or a
non-physical spiritual entity who really
cares it's the messages and information
itself that are important that is where
the value
lies so with that link the introduction
out of the way there were several clips
from this Q&A session that really pequ
my curiosity including this one
concerning anti-gravity technology I'll
link to the full video in the
description below but here's the
clip my question is is the information
available for humans to create uh
anti-gravity propulsion for vehicles to
leave the planet and how could I raise
my my level of being to all right all
right all
right now you can start experimenting
with this yes it's within the realm of
your technology to some degree to begin
with baby steps you have to understand
one principle though the principle is
that location whether up down side side
back forth
whatever the idea of an object being in
a location is incorrect location exists
in the object and words every object has
a shall we say energy equation part of
that energy equation is where and when
it is in time and space if you change
that locational variable the object has
to stop existing where it is and take up
new residence in the new location you
have inserted into the equation so if
you have an overall ability to read very
sensitively the vibrational locational
equation of an object in one position
and then you take that object and raise
it up let's say 6 feet 10 ft whatever
and then you take another reading of its
locational vibration at that level and
you see the difference if you can see
the difference if your equipment is
sensitive enough to see the difference
that difference represents the
difference in location so if you bring
the object back down to the first
location and then you bombard it imbue
it either electromagnetically sonically
however and overwhelm its initial
vibration and in put the idea of the
second location variable vibration the
object will either rise and float up to
that location with no visible means of
support or it will teleport
instantaneously from here to there
that's the secret of anti-gravity is you
have to find the locational variable
within the object thank you very much
you're very
[Applause]
welcome so in that sense it's not
literally
anti-gravity you're just redefining it
location in
space right so wow this idea of each
object having a location property like
an inherent variable really intrigued me
since I never heard of that before it
makes perfect sense though on a big
picture intuitive level but the critical
part of me has a lot of questions
surrounding that for starters how do we
even Define an object is there just one
location variable for the whole object
or do we have to break it down further
than that for example if you wanted to
levitate a car which location are we
talking about exactly the tires the hood
the center point of the car these would
all have different locations so how
granular do we need to be with that I
ask this because scientists are already
doing this at the subatomic level it's
been done many times the fame physicist
mikio Kaku I hope I'm pronouncing that
right uh he confirms this in his 2008
book physics of the impossible where
where he dedicated an entire chapter to
discussing the feasibility of
teleportation now obviously this is a
bit dated now but even back then he
explained that teleportation was already
possible in the lab by exploiting
certain properties of quantum mechanics
such as quantum entanglement and even
more new Agy ideas like vibrational
resonance he concluded that
teleportation exists at the atomic level
and we may eventually teleport complex
and even organic molecules within a few
decades but the teleportation of a
macroscopic object will have to wait for
several decades to centuries beyond that
or longer if it is indeed even
possible so scientists can effectively
teleport subatomic particles like
electrons and photons of light the
challenge is that they're nowhere close
to being able to do this at a
macroscopic level of everyday objects
like people and
cars to reiterate I I feel like the main
thing bashar's premise is overlooking or
glossing over is this idea of what
constitutes an object because given that
macroscopic objects contain trillions
upon trillions of subatomic particles
each with their own precise locations
how then do we determine the overall
location of the entire object is it just
a matter of finding the average of all
the subatomic particles locations which
would be simple in theory but a
nightmare or perhaps outright
impossibility in practice or is it
actually a straightforward as he seems
to suggest that objects we can see in
physical SpaceTime reality actually have
their own inherent location variable
unto themselves does it really resolve
into a single value which would apply to
the entire object this would certainly
be convenient from a technical
standpoint but sounds like a massive
oversimplification so anyway this was
just meant to be a little food for
thought one of my great passions in life
is exploring metaph physics or the
nature of reality whether this comes
from a spiritual perspective or a
scientific perspective doesn't really
matter to me in fact it can be even more
exciting when science touches upon these
big Ideas since as a society we're so
rooted in that and put so much stock on
the scientific method that any progress
or Paradigm shifts on that level would
go a long way towards evolving the
public
Consciousness I definitely plan to cover
more Clips like this from Bashar so stay
tuned and thank you for watching have a
great
[Music]
day